

<u>& 6</u>69-609-161

marcin_nowak_hrx@o2.pl

Kusocińskiego 12/57, Toruń

ABOUT

I have been working as a translator since finishing my MA in English studies, mostly as a freelancer, working with various types of texts, most prominent being film translation. My current main employment is as a purchasing specialist in an international company operating in the heating industry.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office

SAP

Forklift operation

LANGUAGES

POLISH

ENGLISH

INTERESTS

Coding

Fitness

Strategy games

WORK EXPERIENCE

Purchasing specialist in RUG Riello

04.2017 - current

Working with SAP software.

Introducing components into the system.

Ensuring automatisation of orders in the MRP system.

Handling material samples.

Maintaining relations with suppliers.

Negotiating prices and terms of deliveries.

Researching new suppliers.

Translator for Roboto Translation

08.2014 - current

Translation of films is what I have the most experience in, but I have also worked with video games, marketing and training materials. Cooperated with other translators, as well as working on my own. Full-time employment until 2015, freelance since then.

Previous employment in RUG Riello

06.2015 - 04.2017

As an assembly line worker, logistics and internal logistics employee.

Intern in the Rubikon translation agency

09.2011

Working mainly with business and legal texts.

EDUCATION

English studies, MA, specialising In translation. 2012 - 2014

Nicolaus Copernicus University in Toruń

English studies, BA, 2009 - 2012

Nicolaus Copernicus University in Toruń

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumencie do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).